The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Forty-Fifth Episode
The Ghost Ship
A ghost ship!
What?! Has the ghost ship attacked again?
That's already the sixth ship to sink!
What could this ghost ship be?
A sailor who survived
the shipwreck reported...
...that the ghost ship was
commanded by a legendary character!
Legendary? And who would that be?
You’d never guess! The
famous Captain Blood!
Blood?!
Don't tell me that Captain Blood..
. ...is sinking Silverland's ships!
- Exactly!
We even have eyewitnesses!
Speak! Is it true that you saw
Captain Blood on that ship?
Certainly, sir, with our own eyes!
I can't believe it.
Captain Blood has
helped me so many times...
I always thought he was a
generous man, even if a bit rough.
I hope those sailors were mistaken.
Sapphire! I think something is
wrong with him. He looks so depressed!
What happened to you?
What were you thinking about?
About something that needs
to be verified first. Hold on tight!
Wow, look at those beautiful ships!
That should be the one!
- Now he's going to look for Blood.
- Right!
Yes, it's his ship, I recognize it.
How strange... there's
not a living soul on deck!
- Captain Blood!
- Hello, Sapphire!
I recognized your ship.
Why isn't there a sentry?
It could be dangerous!
- So I didn't set a
sentry? Look behind you!
- What was that, boatswain?
- Nothing serious, I slipped
on the rail and fell into the sea!
- The boatswain has
been replaced, Grand Duke!
The secret of the ghost ship
won't be easily discovered!
- Better that way, because otherwise
we would receive a severe reprimand..
. from Mr. X.
- Shut up!
- There is really nothing to
laugh about, Captain Blood!
- But Sapphire, how
could I calmly frequent..
. the port of your Kingdom
if mine were the ghost ship?
- And yet there are
sailors who can testify.
Therefore you could be
arrested at any moment!
- I don't think that would
be possible anymore!
- Good heavens!
The ship has set sail!
Dammit!
I really didn't expect this!
Hey, you two! Ready a new
lifeboat for my friends!
- Yes, sir! - A lifeboat?
- Prepare the sturdiest one
...so they can reach the port
safe and sound.
Captain Blood, wait!
We're not going back to land!
We will find the ghost ship
so we can prove
your innocence!
I refuse your offer!
The sea belongs only to men.
...and a woman profanes it!
Crew, am I not right?
- Yes! Of course! It's true!
- What a backwards mentality!
- Anyway, I'm not going back home!
- You must obey my order!
No! I refuse
and I beg you not to insist!
All right, Princess,
as you wish!
But don't complain,
I warned you!
Count on me! I'll work better
than anyone else on board!
Did you all hear that?
Show no special treatment!
You will treat her
like a member of the crew!
Come on, boys, it's your
first job! Wash these clothes!
You're not telling me that
we have to wash them all?
- Of course! And then you'll sweep the deck!
- Fine. And after that?
Prepare some food,
clean the masts...
Get out of here!
Away!
What did you say
there was to do next?
Clean the mainmast!
What delicacies! What treats!
Captain, this girl
is truly to be admired!
She cooks well and she works
well. She's a respectable sailor!
You're right. In my life
I have never seen a sailor..
...so good and scrupulous
at doing his duty.
I see nothing but sea!
We've been sailing for many days.
Silverland is very far away now.
I wonder what Dad
and Mom are doing, if they are thinking of me..!
Of course they'll be thinking of you!
They'll be worried, in fact!
You have worked well. It seems as if
they have assisted you with their thoughts.
Don't you have any manners?
You must knock before entering!
I did, but you were immersed
in your thoughts...
...and you didn't notice!
- Listen, Captain!
The time has come
to search for the ghost ship!
That is what I will do.
And as soon as I've found it,
I will take the necessary measures
so that it can no longer do harm.
- The ghost ship is in sight!
- There it is!
- Let's go see, quick!
We would do well to get closer!
No, it's dangerous!
Better to approach with a boat!
All right. Prepare a lifeboat,
Let's go take possession
of the ghost ship!
- Hurrah!
- Hooray!
Don't be afraid! It's
the electricity in the air...
...clinging to the ship's masts!
Is anyone on board?
If there's no one there, say no!
- Found anything strange?
- No, sir!
It just seems like an abandoned ship.
Now let's head back on board!
Captain, something doesn't feel right!
Oh, my goodness!
It's not safe to stay here!
I didn't expect to see you here!
But you are the
ship's boatswain!
No, brat,
I’m only his substitute.
Now that you know
the secret of this ship,
we cannot let you go.
Come out!
Don’t worry,
we’ll keep you with us!
You’re coming to Hell Island,
where we live!
To Hell Island!
Tink! Tink!
Come at once
or we’re leaving without you!
Have you seen Tink?
Where did he get to?
I think he’s on the lifeboat
that left earlier.
I searched the ship from top
to bottom, but I didn’t see a soul.
Thanks for the search,
but now let’s go.
It was a trap! Watch out!
Take cover, quickly!
Stay down!
- Help!
- The ghost ship!
- Let's save ourselves!
- Quick, let's run!
- Let's run! Help!
- Help!
Lower the mainsail!
Hard to starboard! Ready to fire!
Men, ready: fire!
Aim for the powder magazine!
Fire!
Take this!
Old sailor..!
This is my last wish,
Sapphire:
Sink the ghost ship!
- Damn you, ghost ship!
- Captain!
- It hit the powder magazine!
- Hurrah!
- Captain, you're great!
- Captain!
- The ship has turned about!
- Let's chase it!
Damn it! It's getting away from us!
It doesn't end here, I'll
make you pay, ghost ship!
This is the rum you liked
so much. And it's top-shelf!
Goodbye, old man!
We'll miss you!
Have you not spotted
the ghost ship yet?
No! I only see
a seagull flying!
What?! A letter?!
I was captured
by a ghost ship.
And taken to an island
called Hell Island!
It's a terrifying place!
There are many men with many weapons
standing guard!
Not even a shark
can get close.
Any ship that enters the bay
is destroyed!
Stay away from here!
I hope this letter
is read by Sapphire!
Try the batteries
of the ghost ship!
Remember...
You must reach the ship
where Sapphire is on board!
So their base
would be Hell Island!
- Do you know it?
- Of course I know it!
It's surrounded
by steep cliffs..
...and has only one inlet
that allows ships to dock!
It's an ideal place to hide
Wait, there's something else!
It says the boatswain is a spy!
I can't believe it!
How can he say these things?
Watch out!
It's the boatswain himself!
I will always be grateful to you, Sapphire,
you saved my life!
Hell Island
is a volcanic island.
The water around the island
is so hot that it boils!
One side of the island
is a very steep cliff.
We will attack there
and surprise them!
That way we will penetrate their lair!
Careful, Sapphire! Hold onto me
or you'll end up overboard!
Ashore, quickly!
Everyone ashore!
Don't look down, Sapphire!
Watch out, there's a sentry!
Be quiet or he'll notice us!
Thanks to your help, the ghost
operation is going perfectly.
But this is only the beginning!
Tonight we drink to
celebrate our next conquest!
No one can attack as long
as we stay on this island!
What the hell is happening?
Look, look,
a party of ghosts!
We'll take them all out!
My brave men, kill him!
Dammit!
Take this!
Sapphire, chase him!
Don't let him escape!
We'll take care of the others!
I will annihilate you, you bastard!
The boss has been killed! Let's run!
Forward, boys!
Give them no rest!
Captain, we are winning!
It's a great victory!
Captain Blood...
Finally! You have the proof of my innocence, Princess Sapphire!
Certainly, I have the proof!
Sapphire!
Well done, Tink!
Thanks to your letter..
...we have avenged the shipwrecked sailors!
What is it, Captain Blood?
Nothing serious, I hope!
Don't worry about me, you know that I am immortal!
Now you two will return home.
My men will accompany you with the ghost ship.
But Captain, I am worried about this wound! It must be treated!
It's a trifle! I'm fine!
Rather, you must hurry to set sail for Silverland,
where you will have to face the enemies of your Kingdom!
- Captain...!
- Go away, please! Go!
All right...
It's my fault they wounded him!
What a magnificent man!
Set sail!
- Goodbye, Princess!
- Bye, Tink! Bye!
- How do you feel, Captain?
- I can make it, friends!
Goodbye and see you soon, Captain!
He is very kind and so generous!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP